Hey guys,
welcome to Day 6 of 100 Days of code. And well done from making it this
far.
So today we're going to talk about code blocks and indentation as well as
functions and also a different flavor from the for loops that we saw yesterday.
Today
we're going to talk about while loops as well. And to learn all of these things,
we're going to use the help of something
that's very similar to Karel the robot.
And this is something I use when I first learnt how to code
and it's one of my favorite tools for learning programming
especially as we get into more difficult concepts like functions and while loops
et cetera. And by the end of the day, we're going to be writing the code
that's required to instruct our little robot to be able to complete any
randomly generated maze. So that's the goal
and if you head over to the next lesson,
let's get started and let's start learning about some of these things.